export const questionArray = [
  {
    question: "What acronym is used for 'Application Program Interface'?",
    answer: "API",
    decoy: ["IBM", "CSS", "ABC", "API"],
  },
  {
    question: "A Boolean can return 'true' and ...?",
    answer: "false",
    decoy: ["say what?", "wrong", "false", "whatever"],
  },
  {
    question: "A 'string' is an example of an ...",
    answer: "data type",
    decoy: ["toy", "data type", "fruit", "API"],
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the best Avenger?",
    answer: "Hulk",
    decoy: ["Iron Man", "Hulk", "Thor", "Black Widow"],
  },
  {
    question: "How many primitive data types are there?",
    answer: "7",
    decoy: ["5", "8", "6", "7"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is an example of a 'loop'?",
    answer: "while",
    decoy: ["whenever", "meanwhile", "justify", "while"],
  },
  {
    question: "What is the acronym for Hypertext Markup Language?",
    answer: "HTML",
    decoy: ["CSS", "JS", "HTML", "HML"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following asks if something is strictly equal?",
    answer: "===",
    decoy: ["==", "===", "!==", "="],
  },
  {
    question: "What does CSS stand for?",
    answer: "Cascading style sheets",
    decoy: [
      "Cascading sheet styles",
      "Cascading style sheets",
      "Computer styling sheets",
      "Computational sheet styles",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "Which is the index value of the first element in an array?",
    answer: "0",
    decoy: ["1", "first", "foo", "0"],
  },
];
